{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/3220","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"3220","name":"Hash Brown Cafe","address":"19458 Conant","zipcode":"48234","owner":"Howard Taylor","licenseNumber":"059943","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"150","coords":"-83.07686,42.43772","geojson":{"id":"3220","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.076862572,42.437716514]},"properties":{"name":"Hash Brown Cafe","owner":"Howard Taylor","address":"19458 Conant","zipcode":"48234","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"High","license_number":"059943","establishmentid":"3220","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"150","most_recent_license_date":"2016-05-02"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"250","name":"Erotic City","address":"19326 Conant Ave.","zipcode":"48234"},{"establishmentid":"3072","name":"Munchee's Mania","address":"19310 Conant Ave.","zipcode":"48234"},{"establishmentid":"4486","name":"Christian Guidance Center","address":"19211 Anglin St.","zipcode":"48234"},{"establishmentid":"51623405","name":"Family Bistro LLC ","address":"19313  Fleming St. ","zipcode":"48234"},{"establishmentid":"1172","name":"Mason Elementary","address":"19635 Mitchell","zipcode":"48234"},{"establishmentid":"1383","name":"NUNNS BAR-B-Q RESTAURANT","address":"19196 CONANT","zipcode":"48234"},{"establishmentid":"3621","name":"Nunn's Bar-B-Que Restaurant II","address":"19196 Conant","zipcode":"48234"},{"establishmentid":"1418","name":"Heavenly Taste","address":"1490 Outer Dr. E.","zipcode":"48203"},{"establishmentid":"1197","name":"Yiu Chan Restaurant","address":"2415 Seven Mile Rd. E.","zipcode":"48234"},{"establishmentid":"249","name":"Fay's Place","address":"19160 Conant","zipcode":"48234"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"61352","inspectionDate":"2023-01-10T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"57310","inspectionDate":"2022-01-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"54676","inspectionDate":"2021-03-22T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-702.11","violationDescription":"UTENSILS and FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be SANITIZED before use after cleaning. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Clean utensil(s) and food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sanitized","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2021-03-23T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"53001","inspectionDate":"2020-09-10T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"50781","inspectionDate":"2020-02-12T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"GRILL AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"48372","inspectionDate":"2019-07-15T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-07-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.14","violationDescription":"(A) Intake and exhaust air ducts shall be cleaned and filters changed so they are not a source of contamination by dust, dirt, and other materials. \n(B) If vented to the outside, ventilation systems may not create a public health HAZARD or nuisance or unLAWful discharge.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Ventilation system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"44975","inspectionDate":"2019-01-22T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.13","violationDescription":"POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be thawed:  Under refrigeration, or under cool running water (<70° F), or as part of cooking process, and total accumulated time above 41° F, for thawed portions, shall not exceed 4 hours.  Any thawing procedure may be used for immediate service for individual consumers order of READY-TO-EAT foods.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Frozen food(s) for thawing","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F thawed or partially thawed","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store under refrigeration."},{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"CEILING","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":""},{"violationCode":"6-501.18","violationDescription":"PLUMBING FIXTURES such as HANDWASHING SINKS, toilets, and urinals shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean. \n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"sink","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":""},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"42883","inspectionDate":"2018-07-11T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-07-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"GRILL AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"4-204.112","violationDescription":"(A)  In a mechanically refrigerated or hot FOOD storage unit, the sensor of a TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE shall be located to measure the air temperature in the warmest part of a mechanically refrigerated unit and in the coolest part of a hot FOOD storage unit.\n(B)  Cold or hot holding EQUIPMENT used for POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be designed to include and shall be equipped with at least one integral or permanently affixed TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE that is located to allow easy viewing of the device's temperature display (EXCEPT, heat lamps, cold plates, steam tables, or other equipment where it is not practical).\n(C)  TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be designed to be easily readable.\n(D)  FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES and water TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES on WAREWASHING machines shall have a numerical scale, printed record, or digital readout in increments no greater than 1C or 2F in the intended range of use. (Pf)\n\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Thermometer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"}]},{"inspectionid":"41175","inspectionDate":"2018-01-04T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Raw animal food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/next to","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-01-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store raw animal foods below and away from foods needing little or no further prep."},{"violationCode":"2-301.14","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall clean their hands and exposed portions of their arms as specified under § 2-301.12 immediately before engaging in FOOD preparation including working with exposed FOOD, clean EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, and unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES (P) and:\n(A)     After touching bare human body parts other than clean hands and clean, exposed portions of arms; (P)\n(B)     After using the toilet room; (P)\n(C)     After caring for or handling SERVICE ANIMALS or aquatic animals as specified in ¶ 2-403.11(B); (P).\n(D)     Except as specified in ¶ 2-401.11(B), after coughing, sneezing, using a handkerchief or disposable tissue, using tobacco, eating, or drinking; (P)\n(E)     After handling soiled EQUIPMENT or UTENSILS; (P)\n(F)     During FOOD preparation, as often as necessary to remove soil and contamination and to prevent cross contamination when changing tasks; (P)\n(G)     When switching between working with raw FOOD and working with READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\n(H)     Before donning gloves for working with FOOD; (P) and\n(I)      After engaging in other activities that contaminate the hands. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Employee(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Did not wash hands","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-01-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Hands shall be washed with hot water and soap for at least 20 seconds after contamination."},{"violationCode":"6-501.114","violationDescription":"The PREMISES shall be free of items that are unnecessary to the operation or maintenance of the establishment such as EQUIPMENT that is nonfunctional, no longer used and free of litter.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Unnecessary item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not removed from facility","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove from facility/premises."}]},{"inspectionid":"39407","inspectionDate":"2017-07-10T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-301.11","violationDescription":"(A) To prevent food contamination FOOD EMPLOYEES shall properly wash their      hands.\n(B) FOOD EMPLOYEES may not contact exposed, READY-TO-EAT FOOD with      their bare hands and shall use suitable UTENSILS such as deli tissue,       spatulas, tongs, single-use gloves, or dispensing EQUIPMENT. (P)\n(C) FOOD EMPLOYEES shall minimize bare hand and arm contact with exposed     FOOD that is not in a READY-TO-EAT form. (Pf)\n\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Ready-to-eat food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Handled with bare hands","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-07-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Suitable utensils or single-use gloves are to be utilized."},{"violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Raw animal food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/next to","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-07-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store raw animal foods below and away from foods needing little or no further prep."},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."}]},{"inspectionid":"37587","inspectionDate":"2016-12-12T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-702.11","violationDescription":"UTENSILS and FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be SANITIZED before use after cleaning. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Clean utensil(s) and food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sanitized","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2016-12-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Equipment/utensils must be sanitized after cleaning."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-25T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"3220"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}